Mss.Rec.75 Mss.Rec.75
American Philosophical Society
Songs from Lac du Flambeau Reservation, Wisconsin
1952, 1956
Mss.Rec.75
American Philosophical Society
2.0 Reel(s)
2 sound tape reels (1 hr., 13 min.): analog, 3 3/4 ips, 2 track, mono; 5 in. and 7 in.
Catfish, Willie
Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch
Lacasse, Fred
Link, Sam
Martin, John
Smart, Frank
Indians of North America--Wisconsin--Music; Love songs; Ojibwa dance; Ojibwa Indians--Music; Peyote songs; Ponca Indians--Music; Ponca Indians--Rites and ceremonies; Powwows; Sound recordings
- Audio recordings
  - Travelling Song, 1956-08-18; 01-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:52; Catfish, Mrs.; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Smart, Frank
    Existence and Location of Originals note
    This file is a compressed, digitized version of the original. The APS Library maintains the original format (Sound tape reel) as well as an uncompressed digitized version of this recording.
    Lac du Flambeau Reservation (Wis.); Ojibwa dance; Ojibwa Indians--Music
  - Brave Dance, ogicidawigawin, 1956-08-18; 01-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:50; Catfish, Mrs.; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Smart, Frank
  - Wooing Song, 1956-08-18; 01-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:10; Catfish, Mrs.; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Smart, Frank
  - Chicken Dance, 1956-08-18; 01-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:08; Catfish, Mrs.; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Smart, Frank
  - Women's War Song, kwenagamon, 1956-08-18; 01-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:15; Catfish, Mrs.; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Smart, Frank
  - War Song, Brave Dance, 1956-08-18; 01-06; 1.0 .mp3; 00:05:50; Catfish, Mrs.; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Smart, Frank
  - Snake Dance, 1956-08-18; 01-07; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:59; Catfish, Mrs.; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Smart, Frank
  - Love Song, 1956-08-18; 01-08; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:46; Catfish, Mrs.; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Smart, Frank
    Lac du Flambeau Reservation (Wis.); Love songs; Ojibwa dance; Ojibwa Indians--Music
  - Ojibwe song, 1956-08-18; 01-09; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:27; Catfish, Mrs.; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Smart, Frank
  - Love Song, 1956-08-18; 01-10; 1.0 .mp3; 00:03:55; Catfish, Mrs.; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Smart, Frank
  - Drum Heating Song from nimetwin (Drum Ceremony), 1956-08-18; 01-11; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:13; Catfish, Mrs.; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Smart, Frank
  - Horse Presentation Song from nimetwin, 1956-08-18; 01-12; 1.0 .mp3; 00:04:27; Catfish, Mrs.; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Smart, Frank
  - Four Rain-dispelling Songs, 1956-08-18; 01-13; 1.0 .mp3; 00:04:50; Catfish, Mrs.; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Smart, Frank
  - Love Song, 1956-08-18; 01-14; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:53; Catfish, Mrs.; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Smart, Frank
  - Ojibwe dance, 1956-08-18; 01-15; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:11; Catfish, Mrs.; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Smart, Frank
    Indians of North America--Michigan--Music; Lac du Flambeau Reservation (Wis.); Ojibwa dance; Ojibwa Indians--Music
  - Powwow dance, 1956-08-18; 01-16; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:03; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch
    Lac du Flambeau Reservation (Wis.); Ojibwa dance; Ojibwa Indians--Music; Powwows
  - Spirit Song, 1956-08-18; 01-17; 1.0 .mp3; 00:04:26; Catfish, Mrs.; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Smart, Frank
  - Ojibwe Song, 1956-08-18; 01-18; 1.0 .mp3; 00:00:51; Catfish, Willie; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch
  - 49 Dance, 1952-08-22; 02-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:17; Brown, George; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Lacasse, Fred; Link, Sam; Martin, John
  - Swan Dance, 1952-08-22; 02-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:00:41; Brown, George; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Lacasse, Fred; Link, Sam; Martin, John
  - Pipe Dance, 1952-08-22; 02-03; 1.0 .mp3; 00:00:56; Brown, George; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Lacasse, Fred; Link, Sam; Martin, John
  - Pipe Dance, 1952-08-22; 02-04; 1.0 .mp3; 00:00:46; Brown, George; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Lacasse, Fred; Link, Sam; Martin, John
  - Deer Dance, 1952-08-22; 02-05; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:13; Brown, George; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Lacasse, Fred; Link, Sam; Martin, John
  - Southwind Dance, 1952-08-22; 02-06; 1.0 .mp3; 00:00:44; Brown, George; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Lacasse, Fred; Link, Sam; Martin, John
  - War Dance, 1952-08-22; 02-07; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:36; Brown, George; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Lacasse, Fred; Link, Sam; Martin, John
  - Fish Dance, 1952-08-22; 02-08; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:04; Brown, George; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Lacasse, Fred; Link, Sam; Martin, John
  - War Dance, 1952-08-22; 02-09; 1.0 .mp3; 00:01:29; Brown, George; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Lacasse, Fred; Link, Sam; Martin, John
  - Two Love Songs, 1952-08-22; 02-10; 1.0 .mp3; 00:06:59; Brown, George; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch; Lacasse, Fred; Link, Sam; Martin, John
    Lac du Flambeau Reservation (Wis.); Love songs; Ojibwa dance; Ojibwa Indians--Music; Powwows
  - Four Ponca Peyote Songs, 02-11; 1.0 .mp3; 00:06:53; Howard, James Henri; Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch
    Peyote songs; Ponca Indians--Music; Ponca Indians--Rites and ceremonies